earncrypto.com 2018-06-23

# EarnCrypto.com | Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

#### Privacy Policy

### What Our Privacy Policy Covers

Please read this privacy policy to learn more about:

  1. What personally identifiable information of yours is collected by Earncrypto.com ("Earncrypto") or by third-party advertisers (together, the "Third-Parties" or individually a "Third-Party" );
  2. How the information is used;
  3. How you can access and change your account information;
  4. How you will receive notice of changes in this privacy policy; and
  5. How to contact Earncrypto.

### Information Collected by Earncrypto

To become a member of Earncrypto, you must join and create an account on the Earncrypto website. The only information that Earncrypto collects is the information you provide through the Earncrypto registration process, and the information you provide when you update your payment options. This information includes your first and last name, your email address, your Internet Protocol Address ("IP address"), your SSN (only used if you are from USA and have earned over $600+ in rewards in a given year - for tax purposes), and other contact information. Your IP address is recorded when you register, so that Earncrypto can enforce its one account per person policy and other provisions of our Terms of Service.

Other information, that does not personally identify you as an individual, is collected by Earncrypto from the website (such as, by way of example, patterns of utilization), and it is exclusively owned by Earncrypto. This information can be utilized by Earncrypto in such manner as Earncrypto, in its sole discretion, deems appropriate.

### Information Sharing & Disclosure

Earncrypto will not share your personal information with the Third-Parties for the purpose of advertising, i.e. sending unsolicited email. Your email address will be used, however, for tracking purposes, when you complete offers, so that Earncrypto can determine that you completed the offers. Earncrypto will also use your email address to send you the Earncrypto newsletters, unless you have opted out of receiving such newsletters by so indicating on the "E-mail Alerts" section of the "My Account" page, within the "Settings" of the Earncrypto website.

### Cookies

Cookies We use "cookies" on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor's hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site. Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies. You may visit the following sites www.aboutads.info/choices and/or www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp to opt-out of cookies.

### Information Provided to Third-Parties or Other Users

Earncrypto.com ("Earncrypto") deals in large part with the Third-Parties. You may be asked by the Third-Parties to give them your personally identifiable information, either when you complete an offer, when you use their websites, or by some other means. Earncrypto is not responsible for information you provide the Third-Parties, and you should read their privacy policies as well before providing them with any such information. Please note, unless otherwise stated, any offer you complete on Earncrypto.com will be with a Third-Party.

### Legal Disclaimer

It is possible that Earncrypto may need to disclose your personally identifiable information from time to time. Specifically, Earncrypto may disclose any information it has about you to legal authorities, your Internet Service Provider, or other harmed parties without your prior permission, if Earncrypto has a good-faith belief that such disclosure is warranted and/or necessary because: (1) you have violated Earncrypto's Terms of Service, (2) you have undertaken actions which are illegal, fraudulent, or otherwise harmful to Earncrypto, its users, or the Third-Parties, or such disclosure is necessary (3) to conform to legal requirements or to comply with the legal process, (4) to protect and defend Earncrypto's rights in any legal, judicial or administrative proceeding; or (5) to enforce the Terms of Service.

### Managing Your Information

You can review the personal information you have provided Earncrypto and make any desired changes to that information by logging in to your account on the Earncrypto website, clicking on the "Settings" link in the "Members Area" drop down of the Earncrypto website, by editing the information, and then by submitting the revised information. You should update Earncrypto on any changes that occur, which would make the information you have provided Earncrypto inaccurate or misleading.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

Notice of all changes that materially affect ways in which your personally identifiable information may be used or shared will be emailed to you or posted on the Earncrypto website. Your continued use of the Earncrypto program after such notices of changes have been sent to you or published on the Earncrypto website constitutes your consent to the changes.

### Third party sites

To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our Web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address, and clickstream information. For further information, consult the privacy policies of:  

### Pollfish

This website uses Pollfish web plugin. Pollfish is an on-line survey platform, through which, anyone may conduct surveys. Pollfish collaborates with Developers of applications for smartphones and website owners in order to have access to users of such applications/websites and address survey questionnaires to them. This website uses and enables Pollfish cookies. When a user connects to this website, Pollfish detects whether the user is eligible for a survey. Data collected by Pollfish will be associated with your answers to the questionnaires whenever Pollfish sents such questionnaires to eligible users. For a full list of data received by Pollfish through this website, please read carefully Pollfish respondent terms located at https://www.pollfish.com/terms/respondent. By using this website you accept this privacy policy document and you hereby give your explicit consent for the placement of a Pollfish cookie in your system and the processing by Pollfish of the aforementioned data. Furthermore, you are informed that you may disable Pollfish operation at any time by using the Pollfish "opt out section" available on Pollfish website or by disabling "third party cookies" from your browser's settings. We once more invite you to check the Pollfish respondent's terms of use, if you wish to have more detailed view of the way Pollfish works works. 

APPLE, GOOGLE AND AMAZON ARE NOT A SPONSOR NOR ARE INVOLVED IN ANY WAY IN THIS CONTEST/DRAW. NO APPLE PRODUCTS ARE BEING USED AS PRIZES.

### Questions & Comments

Unless stated otherwise, Earncrypto's current privacy policy applies to all information that Earncrypto has about you and your account. If you have any questions or comments regarding your privacy or this privacy policy, you should contact Earncrypto prior to providing Earncrypto any personally identifiable information.
